brucelee.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy — Bruce Lee

**Privacy Notice**

 _Effective July 28, 2016_

Bruce Lee Enterprises, LLC (“ **Bruce Lee Enterprises** ”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Notice describes how Bruce Lee Enterprises collects, uses, and shares your information when you use and interact with our Services and applies to persons in the United States and anywhere else in the world who use our Services (“ **Users** ”). Our Privacy Notice governs your access to and use of all Bruce Lee Enterprises operated and controlled websites including [http://www.brucelee.com/](http://www.brucelee.com/), [http://www.bruceleetea.com/](http://www.bruceleetea.com/), and [http://bruceleefoundation.org/](http://bruceleefoundation.org/), and all other online services controlled or provided by Bruce Lee Enterprises (collectively, the “ **Services** ”).

 **Agreement & Eligibility**

 **Your Agreement With Bruce Lee Enterprises**

This Privacy Notice constitutes a binding legal agreement between you, as a User who uses and interacts with the Services, and Bruce Lee Enterprises. Before accessing, using, or interacting with the Services you should carefully review the terms and conditions of this Privacy Notice, as well as our **Terms of Service** , which is incorporated into your agreement with Bruce Lee Enterprises by this reference. This Privacy Notice applies only to the Services, and Bruce Lee Enterprises’ collection, use, disclosure, and protection of your information. It does not apply to third party websites, applications, or services. 

By using or interacting with our Services you signify your consent to our Privacy Notice and Terms of Service, and the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure, and use of your information described. If you do not agree to the terms of our Privacy Notice and Terms of Service, then you may not use or interact with the Services. 

 If you have questions about Bruce Lee Enterprises’ Privacy Notice or practices, or if you need to contact us about the information we collect about you, our contact information is at the end of this Privacy Notice. 

 **Eligibility To Use The Services**

Bruce Lee Enterprises’ Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. You may not use the Services if you are under the age of 13. 

 **Information Collection & Use**

Bruce Lee Enterprises collects information about you through various means, including when you provide information to us and when we automatically collect information about you when you access, use, or interact with the Services. We use this information for a variety of different reasons, including to improve the Services and tailor the Services to you. The types of information Bruce Lee Enterprises may collect include:

 **Information You Provide To Us:**

 **Bruce Lee Newsletter Information:** Bruce Lee Enterprises may require you to subscribe to a newsletter in order to use certain Services (a “ **Bruce Lee Newsletter** ”). We do not require you subscribe to use all of our Services. Bruce Lee Enterprises will collect certain information about you in connection with your subscription to the Bruce Lee Newsletter, which may include Personally Identifiable Information and other information such as a name and/or email address. “ **Personally Identifiable Information** ” refers to information about you that may be used to identify you, such as your: first name, last name, or email address.  Some of the information associated with your subscription to the Bruce Lee Enterprises Newsletter may be displayed publicly. 

**Payment Transaction Information:** We may collect and store information related to your purchases or donations made through our Services. You may provide certain information to complete payments via the Services, including your name, address, credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address (collectively, “ **Payment Information** ”), along with your delivery or shipping address, to complete payment transactions through certain Services.  We consider the Payment Information collected via the Services private and Bruce Lee Enterprises will not make such information public. 

Please note Bruce Lee Enterprises works with Service Providers (as defined below) to operate our online stores and handle payment transactions. Bruce Lee Enterprises does not itself collect or maintain your credit card or other financial account information; this information is handled for Bruce Lee Enterprises by our Service Providers. You are subject to the Privacy Policies and Terms of Service of our Service Providers when shopping for Bruce Lee products or making donations, the terms of which may differ from those of Bruce Lee Enterprises for the Services. Please review the Service Providers’ Privacy Policies and Terms of Service before using their services. 

**Form Information:** We may use forms to request certain information from you in order to perform certain Services, such as your location to assist you in locating our products, or your contact information to assist with contacts or service requests. This information may include Personally Identifiable Information. 

**Correspondence Information:** If you sign up, email us, subscribe to our newsletters or mailing lists, or make donations or purchases through the Services, we may keep your message, email address, and contact information to respond to your requests, provide the requested products or Services, and to provide notifications or other correspondences to you. We do not share or sell any personal information to other organizations for commercial purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, you may opt-out of receiving certain communications from Bruce Lee Enterprises by following the unsubscribe process described in the email communication. We may also still contact you as needed to provide important announcements or notifications regarding the Services.

 **Support Information:** You may provide information to us via a support request submitted through the Services. We will use this information to assist you with your support request and may maintain this information to assist you or other Users with support requests. Please do not submit any information to us via a support submission, including confidential or sensitive information that you do not wish for Bruce Lee Enterprises or our Service Providers to have access to or use in the future.

 **Information We Collect Automatically:**

 **Cookies, Web Beacons, Links, And Other Tracking Technologies:** Bruce Lee Enterprises may keep track of how you use and interact with the Services through the use of cookies, web beacons, links, and other tracking technologies.  We do this to help analyze the use of and improve the Services. Through these technologies we may automatically collect information about your use of the Services and other online activities, including our email correspondences, third-party services, and client applications, and certain online activities after you leave the Services. Link information is generally only analyzed on an aggregate basis. Some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies. 

**Unique Identifiers:** When you use or access the Services, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "Unique Identifiers," such as a universally unique identifier (“UUID”). A Unique Identifier may remain on your device persistently, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Services. Some features of the Services may not function properly if use or availability of Unique Identifiers is impaired or disabled.

 **Log File Information:** When you use our Services, we may receive log file information such as your IP address, browser type, access times, domain names operating system, the referring web page(s), pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information. We receive log file data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, or interact with our email notifications. Bruce Lee Enterprises uses log file data to provide, understand, and improve our Services, and to customize the content we show you. Bruce Lee Enterprises may link this log file to other information Bruce Lee Enterprises collects about you via the Services. 

**Public Information:** Bruce Lee Enterprises may also collect information about you from publicly available sources. Information you make publicly available in any public or open forum, such as on a social network, may be considered public information for the purposes of this Privacy Notice, and may be accessed and collected by Bruce Lee Enterprises. Please be aware that any content or information you share with or provide to third parties using or related to your use of the Services is nether private, nor confidential. Bruce Lee Enterprises is not responsible for any content or information you post or share with third parties. If you do not wish for certain information to be public, please do not share it. 

**­­­­Information Sharing**

Bruce Lee Enterprises will not share, sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your private personal information to third parties without your consent, except in the limited circumstances described in this Privacy Notice, including to:

 **Bruce Lee Enterprises Personnel:** Bruce Lee Enterprises’ personnel may have access to your information as needed to provide and operate the Services in the normal course of business. This includes information regarding your use and interaction with the Services. ** **

 **Service Providers:** Bruce Lee Enterprises works with various organizations and individuals to help provide the Services to you (" **Service Providers** "), such as hosting companies, e-commerce shopping website providers to provide the online shops available via the Services, payment processors to process payments, and companies providing analytics information, like Google Analytics. We may share your personal information with our Service Providers for the purpose of providing the Services. The information we share to our Service Providers may include both information you provide to us and information we collect about you, including Personally Identifiable Information, Payment Information (to payment processing providers only), information from data collection tools like cookies, web beacons, log files, Unique Identifiers, and location data. Bruce Lee Enterprises takes reasonable steps to ensure that our Service Providers are obligated to reasonably protect your information on Bruce Lee Enterprises’ behalf. If Bruce Lee Enterprises becomes aware that a Service Provider is using or disclosing information improperly, we will take commercially reasonable steps to end or correct such improper use or disclosure.

 **Online Shops:**  Bruce Lee Enterprises works with third party Service Providers to operate our online stores and handle payment transactions. When you click links such as “Shop” or “Donate” within our Services, you are redirected to one of our third party Service Provider’s platforms to shop and complete purchases. Bruce Lee Enterprises does not itself collect or maintain your credit card or other financial account information; this information is handled for Bruce Lee Enterprises by our Service Providers. Bruce Lee Enterprises does not collect additional information about you when you are using our Service Providers’ services, but our Service Providers may share certain information they collect about you with Bruce Lee Enterprises as part of your use of their services, such as information about customers who have made purchases after using Bruce Lee Enterprises’ Services. Please note you are subject to the Privacy Policies and Terms of Service of our Service Providers, including when shopping for Bruce Lee products or making donations, the terms of which may differ from those of Bruce Lee Enterprises for the Services. Please review the Service Providers’ Privacy Policies and Terms of Service before using their services.

 **Business Transactions:** Bruce Lee Enterprises may purchase other businesses or their assets, sell our business assets, or be involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets (a “ **Business Transaction** ”). Your information, including Personally Identifiable Information, may be among assets sold or transferred as part of a Business Transaction. 

  **Lawful Requests:** We may be required to disclose User information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We generally do not disclose User information unless we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. We may share your information when we believe it is necessary to comply with applicable laws, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Services or using the Bruce Lee Enterprises name, or to protect the safety of any person. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or government agencies. Nothing in this Privacy Notice is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

 **Accessing & Modifying Your Information**

 **Access To The Information Bruce Lee Enterprises Has Collected About You**

Bruce Lee Enterprises welcomes you to contact us regarding the information we have collected about you, including regarding the nature and accuracy of the data has collected about you, or to request an update or deletion of your information. Requests to delete or remove your information do not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted, and removed information may persist in backup copies indefinitely. Please note that if you choose to delete your information or opt-out of the collection and use of your information, you understand that certain features, including but not limited to access to the Services, may no longer be available to you. 

We may store the information we collect about you indefinitely, but information generally will be retained only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected, or as otherwise required by law. 

**Opting-Out Of Communications From Bruce Lee Enterprises**

Users may opt-out of receiving certain communications from Bruce Lee Enterprises by following the unsubscribe process described in an email communication. However, please note you may not opt-out of Services-related communications, such as account verification, purchase and billing confirmations, changes or updates to features of the Services, or technical and security notices. 

**Do Not Track**

Bruce Lee Enterprises does not currently employ a process for automatically responding to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals sent by web browsers, mobile devices, or other mechanisms. Per industry standards, third parties may be able to collect information, including Personally Identifiable Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services when you use Services. You may opt out of online behavioral ads at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You also may limit certain tracking by disabling cookies in your web browser.

 **Information Security**

 **Security Of Your Information**

Bruce Lee Enterprises takes reasonable efforts to secure and protect the privacy, accuracy, and reliability of your information and to protect it from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Bruce Lee Enterprises implements security measures as we deem appropriate and consistent with industry standards. When personal information (such as a credit card or bank account number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. As no data security protocol is impenetrable, Bruce Lee Enterprises cannot guarantee the security of our systems or databases, nor can we guarantee that personal information we collect about you will not be breached, intercepted, destroyed, accessed, or otherwise disclosed without authorization. Accordingly, any information you transfer to or from Services is provided at your own risk. 

  **Additional Provisions Regarding The Services & Your Information **

  **Transfer And Storage Of Your Information**

Please note information Bruce Lee Enterprises collects about you may be transferred, processed and/or accessed by us in the United States, or another country where we, or our Service Providers operate. Please be aware Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state or country where privacy laws may differ from and may not be as protective as those where you live. If you are located outside the United States and choose to allow us to collect information about you, please be aware that Bruce Lee Enterprises may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to the United States and process and store it there. By allowing collection of your Personally Identifiable Information, you consent to having your personal data transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States. 

If you are located in the European Economic Area ("EEA") or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information to a country or jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of Service Providers. By submitting your information, registering for, or using the Services, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States, or any other country in which Bruce Lee Enterprises or our Service Providers maintain facilities, and to the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Notice.

 **Safely Using Bruce Lee Enterprises’ Services**

Despite Bruce Lee Enterprises’ safety and privacy controls, we cannot guarantee the Services are entirely free of illegal, offensive, pornographic, or otherwise inappropriate material, or that you will not encounter inappropriate or illegal conduct from other Users when using the Services. You can help Bruce Lee Enterprises by notifying us of any unwelcome contact by contacting us using the information below.   

 **Changes to Our Privacy Notice**

Bruce Lee Enterprises may, in its sole discretion modify or revise this Privacy Notice from time to time. The most current version of this policy will govern our use of your information and will be located here. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Notice.

 **Contact Bruce Lee Enterprises**

Bruce Lee Enterprises, LLC

9854 National Blvd. Suite 181

Los Angeles, CA 90034

 **Contact Us**
